question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "French is an official language in Canada.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
